Finally, your 90-day audio. This, again, is part of the whole package.
If I'm going to create a Theta track, I'm going to choose
what my targets are for the, for the, for the quarter.
Now, these are getting fed for my quarterly targets that I set
up, or I could simply overwrite these and change them.
If I continue, I have my targets that are here. I get
to choose. I can choose how I want the AI to talk
to me.
Motivation, calm, energizing. What this is going to do, it's going to
give you an AI track that's 21 minutes that you can download
as MP3 and share it directly to your phone.
And every morning, you have an AI voice repeating your targets to
you in a way through IM statements, so you can manifest them
and make those real.
So when I click on Generate Affirmations, it's going to generate the
affirmations based upon my targets that I made inside the quarter.
After it generates my affirmations, I can confirm that I like them
or I can have them regenerated. And then I simply move on
to choose what is the voice that I'm going to have inside
of this.
If I hit play, I believe in my potential. I am capable
of achieving my goals. I can hear the voice.
And if I like that one, I can choose that one and
say, let's do it. Once I continue, this is where I will
generate my Theta track.
It takes probably three to four minutes. And you're going to have
a downloaded track for you to listen to essentially with music behind
the background in a meditative way for you to empower yourself massively.